[RINGING SOUND]
[♪♪♪]
♪ The club isn't the best place
to find a lover ♪
♪ So the bar is where I go ♪
♪ Me and my friends at
the table doing shots ♪
♪ Drinking fast and
then we talk slow ♪
♪ Come over and start up a
conversation with just me ♪
♪ And trust me I'll give it
a chance now ♪
♪ Take my hand, stop, put
Van the Man on the jukebox ♪
♪ And then we start to dance,
and now I'm singing like ♪
♪ Girl, you know
I want your love ♪
♪ Your love was handmade
for somebody like me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ I may be crazy,
don't mind me ♪
♪ Say, boy, let's not
talk too much ♪
♪ Grab on my waist and
put that body on me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ Come, come on now,
follow my lead ♪
♪ I'm in love with
the shape of you ♪
♪ We push and pull
like a magnet do ♪
♪ Although my heart
is falling too ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ And last night
you were in my room ♪
♪ And now my bedsheets
smell like you ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ (Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I) ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with
the shape of you ♪
♪ One week in
we let the story begin ♪
♪ We're going out on
our first date ♪
♪ You and me are thrifty,
so go all you can eat ♪
♪ Fill up your bag and
I fill up a plate ♪
♪ We talk for hours and hours
about the sweet and the sour ♪
♪ And how your family
is doing OK ♪
♪ And leave and get in a taxi,
then kiss in the backseat ♪
♪ Tell the driver make the radio
play, and I'm singing like ♪
♪ Girl, you know
I want your love ♪
♪ Your love was handmade
for somebody like me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ I may be crazy,
don't mind me ♪
♪ Say, boy, let's not
talk too much ♪
♪ Grab on my waist and
put that body on me ♪
♪ Come on now, follow my lead ♪
♪ Come, come on now,
follow my lead ♪
♪ I'm in love with
the shape of you ♪
♪ We push and pull
like a magnet do ♪
♪ Although my heart
is falling too ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ And last night you
were in my room ♪
♪ And now my bedsheets
smell like you ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ (Oh-I-oh-I-oh-I-oh-I) ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with
the shape of you ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ I'm in love with
the shape of you ♪
♪ We push and pull
like a magnet do ♪
♪ Although my heart
is falling too ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ And last night
you were in my room ♪
♪ And now my bedsheets
smell like you ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with your body ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby
- (I'm in love with your body) ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby
- (I'm in love with your body) ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby, come on ♪
♪ Come on, be my baby
- (I'm in love with your body) ♪
♪ Every day discovering
something brand new ♪
♪ I'm in love with
the shape of you ♪
[COSTUME RUSTLES]
[HE GROANS]